[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What do we think we know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "There are a lot of rumors flying around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Do you have any update on how she is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "She's fine, and that's -- it's according to family members and according to reports.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "And just one more thing, Piers, I want to tell you about, those photographs, you know, the club that you -- that you've been talking about and we've been reporting on, this new nightclub?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CD", "RBR", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "How do you feel about the fact you did the last interview with Whitney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Piers, it's -- I am still in shock.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "You do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "He's the producer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Yes, that's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "CD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 148, "question": "Why did you feel that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 149, "answer": "Well, it's as though -- as much as I am spiritual and do celebrate death to some extent, you know, I celebrate -- I look at it more as like a graduation, out of the flesh into spirit, and then freeing one up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "As one of her close friends, how do you feel about what was being allowed to happen to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Was she very vulnerable, do you think, Whitney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Even to the end to that kind of situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, it's all of the above and a whole lot more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Would she have gone down that route, do you think, without Bobby Brown in her life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, if not him, somebody else.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby Brown"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "And do you think she had that tendency anyway?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I think that we all as artist, because we're highly sensitive people, and this machine around us, this so-called music industry, is such a demonic thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Have you been through that process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What is it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "It -- let me tell you, I had polyps on my throat from like smoking, drinking and things like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What do you think that did to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "It killed her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "That must have been agony for her that she couldn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "It was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Were you surprised or has this been the kind of news that many of her friends have long feared may suddenly be brought upon then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "I have to be honest with you and say, that there were -- with my life, it's just as not as well publicized as with her life, there are a lot of parallels, where I'm sure my family thought like her family thought and I thought, oh, my god, I mean, I've cried for her a lot over the years, so many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Would she listen -- would she listen to people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "And what was her defense really of her actions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "HAN: She had no defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "How is she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "She's coping, she's coping.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "What did you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I thought that was complete insanity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "What is your abiding memory of Whitney Houston?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "They're all really good ones.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "What do you think has been the biggest misconception about Whitney that you have heard or read in the last 36 hours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I would say being in the studio with Whitney Houston and meeting her for the first time, what I want people to concentrate on is her natural warmth for humanity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "In terms of the issues that she had to deal with, how much of an impact do you think that had on her natural talent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "I think for me, being in the studio with her and understanding the stress we artists go through at times -- it's not the first time in history that -- you know, where we feel the pressure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "How would you like her as an artist to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I would like her to be remembered -- me and Whitney, beyond music, I think what we share, my father is a preacher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney"]}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "What I would say is the Whitney that I know and being in the studio with her, what I want we to understand as human beings is that we are human, and we are quick to judge.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "What are your feelings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, it's still so hard for all of us to believe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby Brown"]}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, I -- I can say this, that we were all around a lot of drugs and that she had -- I hate to say that she had started before she had met Bobby Brown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "That's the sadness here, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What was it like in reality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "In reality, she was very busy, extremely busy, having to go here, having to go there, especially in the hey-day when so much was happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Do you think that the pressure of being Whitney Houston just became too much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "I think it's intense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Whitney Houston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["northern California", "Gualala", "Whitney"]}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "NN", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "When you heard she died, what was your emotion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I was in a bathtub, way up in northern California, place called Gualala (ph), and on a little transistor radio they said that Whitney had died.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Do you feel it's a wasted life or do you feel it was a short but brilliant life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Short but brilliant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Did you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]